hiox.org 2014-10-23

# Privacy Policy - Hiox.org

Authenticating...

Following describes privacy practices specific to Hiox.org.

### Personal Information

  * **Browsing Hiox.org** You can view the contents on Hiox.org without having a Hiox.org Account. 
  * **Your Hiox.org Account.** For some activities on Hiox.org, like, posting comments, content you need a Hiox.org account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 
  * **Usage Information.** When you use Hiox.org, we may record information about your usage of the site, favorites you subscribe to, the content you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in Hiox.org (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your Hiox.org Account. 
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online may be collected and used by others.
  * If you submit personal information to Hiox.org, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of Hiox.org, and to process communications you send to us.
  * We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Hiox.org changes or for customer service purposes).

### Information that is publicly available

  * When you create a Hiox.org Account, some information about your Hiox.org Account profile without the email address will be provided to other users of Hiox.org. 
  * Your Hiox.org Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on Hiox.org, such as when you send messages through Hiox.org. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.
  * If you have a Hiox.org Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page.
  * You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through Hiox.org. But Hiox.org may not be able to provide certain services to you. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

### More Information

Hiox.org adheres to the law of Government of India privacy principles.  
For more information about our privacy practices write to us at:

Hiox.org Privacy Policy  
HIOXINDIA,  
No.7A-F, Ganesha Complex campus,  
N.K.Palayam Road,  
Singanallur,  
Coimbatore,  
Tamilnadu, INDIA.  
PinCode - 641005.  
please contact us at [support@hiox.org](mailto:support@hiox.org)
